whitetruffle.com 2014-06-26

# Whitetruffle | Privacy Policy

We at Whitetruffle, Inc. ("Whitetruffle," "we," "us," "our") know that our users ("you," "your") care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the www.whitetruffle.com website and domain name, and any other linked pages, features, content, mobile applications, or any other services we offer from time to time by in connection therewith (collectively, the "Website," or the “Services”), in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.

#### I. What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@whitetruffle.com](mailto:support@whitetruffle.com).

#### II. What Information Does Whitetruffle Collect?

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this Personal Information to personalize and improve our services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how users utilize the Website and Product, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties (as described in this Section and in Section III below). We collect the following types of information:

##### A. Information You Provide to Us:

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, we collect Personal Information such as your name, user name, email address, contact information, employment history and details, resume, and personal preferences regarding employment, and we may collect other employment-related information as our services and products are further developed. If you provide your third-party account credentials to us or sign in through a third party website or service, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts ("Third Party Account Information") may be transmitted into your account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Website is covered by this Privacy Policy. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our of our features.

##### B. Information Collected Automatically:

  * Whenever you interact with our Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, "cookie" information, and the page you requested. "Cookies" are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our Website are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of our Website's best features.
  * When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Website), we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users use parts of the Website, so that we can make the Website appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often people use our Website, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

##### C. E-mail and Other Communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may send you promotional offers on behalf of other businesses, or communicate with you about your use of the Website or the Product. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make emails more interesting and improve our service. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by emailing us at [support@whitetruffle.com](mailto:support@whitetruffle.com).

#### III. Will Whitetruffle Share Any of the Personal Information It Receives?

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form with third parties only as described below.

##### A. Affiliated Businesses and Third Party Websites We Do Not Control:

In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we're affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through the Website (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. One such service may include the ability for you to choose to automatically transmit Third Party Account Information to your Website profile or to automatically transmit information in your Website profile to your third party account.

We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to allow these automatic transmissions, please review all third party websites' policies.

##### B. Agents:

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

##### C. User Submissions, User Profiles, and Interaction With Employers and Affiliates:

User profile information including, without limitation, your name, email address and other contact information, employment history and other employment details (including information that may have been automatically transmitted to your Website account from a third party site or service) (“User Profile Information”), may be displayed to Employers (as that term is defined in our Terms of Use http://www.whitetruffle.com/terms) in accordance with the preferences you have indicated and the functionality of the Website, in order to facilitate interaction between you and Employers. For example, an Employer will tell us what type of candidate it is looking for, and if your employment history matches the Employer's criteria, we will display an anonymized version of your resume and employment history and details to such Employer (i.e., without your name or contact information). If the Employer is interested in contacting you, we will ask you whether you want to be contacted by that Employer. If you do, we will give your contact information to the Employer, but we only authorize Employers to contact you for the purposes of discussing potential employment, and for no other reason.

You may register with us through a landing page on our Website that is associated with one of our referral affiliates (an “Affiliate”). If you do so, your User Profile Information may also be displayed to the applicable Affiliate, in accordance with the preferences you have indicated and the functionality of the Services. For example, when you register through an Affiliate, you may be given the option to display your real name and other User Profile Information (which, in the case of Affiliates, may also include your history of employment placements made through our Services) to such Affiliate, so that they may communicate with you regarding our Services and keep track of the successes you’ve had through our Services.

##### D. Business Transfers:

We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

##### E. Protection of Whitetruffle and Others:

We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with laws; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Whitetruffle, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

##### F. With Your Consent:

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

#### IV. Is Personal Information About Me Secure?

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site's privacy policy.

#### V. What Personal Information Can I Access?

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you've provided to us:

  * name and password
  * email address and contact information
  * user profile information, including your employment details

The information you can view and update may change as the Website changes. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at [support@whitetruffle.com](mailto:support@whitetruffle.com).

#### VI. What Choices Do I Have?

  * You can always opt not to disclose information to use, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features.
  * You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained in Section V above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Please note that some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.
  * You may request deletion of your account with Whitetruffle by emailing us at [support@whitetruffle.com](mailto:support@whitetruffle.com).
  * If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please email us at [support@whitetruffle.com](mailto:support@whitetruffle.com). Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website and the Product, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. Please also note that once Employers have your contact information, we are not able to control the manner or frequency in which they contact you; if you would like to stop receiving messages from Employers, please indicate your preference to those Employers directly.

#### VII. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website or the Product after such changes have been first posted.

#### VIII. Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to [support@whitetruffle.com](mailto:support@whitetruffle.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

##### Effective June 27, 2011
